Donald G. Adams Papers, Inclusive: 1962-1980, undated, Bulk: 1972-1977, undated
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1967-1977, undated; 5
  - 64th Legislature, 1971-1976, undated; 4
    - SB 4, Licensing Requirements for Installing Alarms, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - SB 5, Licensing Requirements for Companies Installing and Running Alarm Systems, 1975, undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - SB 6, Tax Exemption for Agricultural Supplies, 1975, undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - SB 7, Incorporation, Boundaries, and Proceedings of Towns, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - SB 32, Parent-Child Relationship, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - SB 33, Determining Paternity, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - SB 702, Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - SB 702, Actuarial Information and Correspondence, 1975-1977, undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - SB 702, Bill Drafts, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Old Version of SB 702, Volunteer Firefighters’ Relief and Retirement Fund, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - SB 702, Correspondence with Fire Department Leaders, 1974-1976, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - SR 325, Designating Dogwood Week in Texas, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - SJR 2, Judicial Review for Administrative Agency Decisions, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - 65th Legislature, 1975-1977, undated; 5
    - "Senate Journal", 1977 April 18-19 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - SB 3, Prohibition of Charges for Telephone Directory Services, SJR 4, Incurring State Debt, SCR 4, Right-to-Work, 1977, undated (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - SB 20, Old Age and Survivors Insurance, State Employees, 1977, undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - SB 33, Use of Generic Names for Prescription Drugs, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - SB 34, Effect of Speeding Violations on Driver’s License Suspensions and Insurance Rates, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - SB 39, SB 40, SB 78, SB 95, SB 354, SB931 and HB 2059, SB 1125, SB 1139, SB 1234, Business, Labor, Appropriations, Utilities, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - SB 63 and SB 91, Creating State Formulary Commission and School-Community Guidance Center Pilots, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - SB 66, Power of a Court to Grant Independent Administration of a Decedent’s Estate, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - SB 70, Retired Peace Officers Carrying Handguns, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - SB 74, Texas Education Code, Retirement Benefits, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - SB 103, Enactment of the Medical Liability and Insurance Improvement Act of Texas, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - SB 152, Probation and Parole Conditions, undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - SJR 1 and SB 1, Valuation of Agricultural and Forest Lands for Tax Purposes, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - SJR 2, Texas Constitution Amendment, Establishment of Bingo Games and Raffles for Non-Profit Organizations, Clippings and Case Law, 1971-1977, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - SJR 2, Texas Constitution Amendment, Establishment of Bingo Games and Raffles for Non-Profit Organizations, Correspondence, Notes, and Reports, 1975-1977, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - SJR 38 and SJR 49, Authorize Additional Colleges in University of Texas System and Banking and Discounting Privileges for Electronic Devices, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - SCR 24, Recall of Equal Rights Amendment, 1976-1977, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - CSSB 60 and SB 61, Texas Colleges to Contract with Teaching Hospitals and Probationer Reimbursing County for Court-Appointed Counsel, 1977, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - CSSB 1207, Natural Resources Code (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - CSSB 1207, Natural Resources Code (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - HB 17, Refinery Tax, 1976-1977, undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - HB 1048, Medical Liability and Insurance Improvement Act of Texas, General (1 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - HB 1048, Medical Liability and Insurance Improvement Act of Texas, General (2 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - HB 1048, Medical Liability and Insurance Improvement Act of Texas, Uher’s Motion and Amendment, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - HB 1048, Medical Liability and Insurance Improvement Act of Texas, Texas Medical Association Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - State Fireman’s Pension Commissioner, Department Inventories, 1975-1977 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Personal and Memorial Resolutions (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Personal and Memorial Resolutions (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - SB 29, Mission Senora Dolores de los Ais, 1976-1977 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - SB 29, Mission Senora Dolores de los Ais, 1977, undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - SB 30, Legitimacy and Birth Certificates, 1976-1977 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - SB 47, Amending State Purchasing Act of 1957, 1976-1977 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - SB 48, Creation of a Firefighters’ Relief and Retirement Fund, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - SB 68, Utility Funds for Steven F. Austin State University, 1976-1977 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - SB 76, Unloading Requirement for Timber Vehicles, 1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - SB 85, Number of Days in the School Year, 1976-1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - SB 96, Bag and Retention Limits for Squirrels, Angelina County, 1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - SB 97, Senate Sitting as Court of Impeachment, 1976-1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - SB 98, Open Season for Fur-Bearing Animals, Cherokee County, 1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - SB 100, Search Warrants for Texas Water Quality Board Inspections, 1976-1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - SB 104, Creating County Court District, Jasper and Newton Counties, 1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - SB 125, Angelina and Neches River Authority, 1976-1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - SB 126, Creating County Court District, Sabine and St. Augustine, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - SB 144, Regulation of Public Surveyors, 1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - SB 145, Lien of Workmen for Improvement of Property, 1975-1977 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - SB 200, Immunity for Witnesses before the Legislature, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - SB 206, Election of the Board of Supervisors, Panola County Fresh Water Supply District, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - SB 231, Sales Tax Exemption for Volunteer Fire Departments, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - SB 340, Immunity from Suits for Steven F. Austin State University, 1976-1977 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - SB 486, Submission to State Board of Control of Plans for Erecting Monuments, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - SB 545, Giving 3.69 miles of the Texas State Railroad to the City of Palestine, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - SB 615, Consumer Credit Reform Act, Notes, Research, and Responses, 1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - SB 615, Consumer Credit Reform Act, Reports, 1976-1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - SB 615, Consumer Credit Reform Act, Correspondence, Clippings, and Press Releases, 1977, undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - SB 615, Consumer Credit Reform Act, Senate Commission on Economic Development, Testimony and Minutes, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - SB 615, Consumer Credit Reform Act, Committee Testimony, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - SB 615, Consumer Credit Reform Act, Bill Drafts, 1977, undated (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - SB 1179, Conflicts of Interest, State Banking Board, Finance Commission of Texas and State Depository Board, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - SB 1180, Creation and Organization of Hospital Districts, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - SB 1248, Political Advertising, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - SB 1286, Maintenance of Bonds, Insurance, and Renewal of Licenses in the Regulation of Liquified Petroleum, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - SB 1335, Hearings on Orders of the Texas Water Quality Board, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - SR 335, Subcommittee on Nominations Holding Meetings during the Interim, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - SCR 45, Boundary Marker for 1841 United States-Texas Border, National Historic Landmark, 1976-1977, undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - SB 28, 5-Year Prohibition of Turkey Hunting in Shelby County, 1976-1977 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - SB 29, Designation of Official Site of Mission Dolores de los Ais, 1972-1976 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - SB 48, Creation of Firefighters’ Relief and Retirement Fund, General, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - SB, 48, Creation of Firefighters' Relief and Retirement Fund, Drafts, 1976, undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - SB, 48, Creation of Firefighters' Relief and Retirement Fund, Correspondence, 1976-1977, undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - SB, 48, Creation of Firefighters' Relief and Retirement Fund, Committee Substitute, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - SB 411, Firefighters’ Relief and Retirement Fund, General, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - SB 411, Firefighters’ Relief and Retirement Fund, Drafts, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - SB 411, Firefighters’ Relief and Retirement Fund, Committee Substitute, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - SB 411, Firefighters’ Relief and Retirement Fund, Committee Amendments, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - SB 411, Firefighters’ Relief and Retirement Fund, Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - SB 659, Use and Allocation of Cigarette Tax Revenue, 1977, undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - SB 660, Creation of New Judicial District, Jasper, Newton, and Tyler Counties, 1977, undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - SB 701, Authority of Capitol Security Officers to Carry Firearms, 1977, undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - SB 713, Election of Directors of the Sabine County Hospital District, 1977, undated (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - SB 729, Membership of the Board of Law Examiners and the Fee for a Bar Exam, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - SB 771, Prior Work Experience for Teachers, Salary Increments and Teacher Retirement, 1976-1977 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - SB 810, Designation of the Official Site of Mission Nuestra Senora de los Dolores de los Ais, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Personal, 1966-1980, undated; 6
  Series VI. Personal contains various information related to Adams's private life rather than his career of public service. The series is divided into four loose topics, around which the materials are organized. The General topic set includes financial dealings, personal correspondence, and information on Adams's published book "How a Bill Becomes a Law". The Legal Proceedings topic set contains material related to Adams's legal career and case files from his law firm. The Political Figures topic set consists of subject files Adams collected concerning major political figures such as John Dowdy, John Hannah, and Charles Wilson. Lastly, the Speeches topic set contains speech transcripts and outlines from speaking engagements during Adams's tenure as a State Representative from 1967 to 1970. Overall, this series is in good condition.
  - Personal Correspondence, 1971-1975, undated (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Investment Information, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Study, “Benefit Plans in Junior College”, by Francis P. King, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Five Outstanding Young Texans, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Calendars, June-December, 1971, undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - How a Bill Becomes a Law (Nugent and Adams Book), 1972 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Financial Disclosure Request, 1969-1971, undated (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Legal Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Auto Insurance Litigation — Cottrelletal vs. Cecil & Larry Nix, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Brookeland Missionary Baptist Church Building Loan, 1977-1980 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Harry Conley v. Stone & Webster, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Charles Frazier v. Sandra Frazier — Custody Lawsuit, 1976-1980, undated (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - John Hannah, 1969-1971 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - John Hannah, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - John Dowdy, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Charles Wilson, 1969-1971 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Speeches and Source Material, 1966-1969, undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Speeches and Source Material, 1970, undated (Box 60, Folder 5)